http://www.ioimelaw.com/privacy-statement

Skip to main content
Search form
Search
"My job as a lawyer is not to get my clients out of trouble, but to make sure they do not get into trouble."
Privacy Statement
Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationDaniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law Web site.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law does not read any of your private online communications.Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law and Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law family of Web sites.Use of your Personal InformationDaniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law collects and uses your personal information to operate the Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law and its affiliates. Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law, in order to determine what Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law, or the public.Use of CookiesThe Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law pages, or register with Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law site or services, a cookie helps Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law services or Web sites you visit.Security of your Personal InformationDaniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to this StatementDaniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law is protecting your information.Contact InformationDaniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Daniel C. Ioime, Attorney at Law at dan@ioimelaw.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
The Law Office of Daniel C. Ioime, LLCOne Evergreen Avenue, Suite LL-6 Hamden, Connecticut 06518
Busy theme for Drupal.
